mockbank.com 2013-12-16

# Privacy Policy | MockBank- Mock tests for banking and PSU exams- IBPS, RBI, SEBI, NABARD, LIC, NIC, SSC, UPSC etc.

**MockBank Privacy Policy**

Thank you for visiting www.MockBank.com, (the “Site”). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the way your information is collected and used at www.MockBank.com. Your membership in and use of www.MockBank.com indicates your understanding of and agreement with, the policy expressed herein.

www.MockBank.com is owned and operated by MockBank, a Gurgaon based sole proprietorship firm. MockBank respects the privacy of visitors to the Site and the security of the data that visitors provide. This Privacy Policy explains what type of information we collect, and what we do with that information. The Privacy Policy may change from time to time so please check it frequently.

_The Information We Collect_

The types of personally identifiable information that we may collected at the Site include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, educational background, employment preferences, date of birth, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows ’95 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., MTS, Airtel).

_With Whom Do We Share Information?_

Other companies that provide services on our Site, or that advertise or link on our Site, may use cookies or collect other information about you when you go to their Site. MockBank does not control the collection or use of information by these companies. You should contact these companies directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies or their collection or use of information about you.

_How We Use the Information_

We collect your personal information at the time of registration. The information you provide is used for your profiling and conducting the need assessment that may suggest other courses that may be of interest to you or for providing you with information regarding other relevant mock assessments in future. We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you about changes to our assessment methodology, to fulfill a request by you for an inquiry, or to contact you about your account with us. It will also be used to facilitate and fulfill your work for conducting the mock assessment and creating and validating your credential in the assessment engine.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a notice. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request. Agents and contractors of MockBank who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy, by for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for MockBank

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. You understand and agree that you are entering your personal information aware of and willing to accept risks associated with the provision of that information including but not limited to unauthorized or unintended disclosure of that information, and that you release and hold harmless MockBank, their officers, agents, employees, attorneys, managers and those acting on their behalf of and from all debts, demands, actions, cause of actions, suits, damages, and any and all claims, demands and liability whatsoever of any nature both in law and equity against each other which either party now has or has ever had to this date, including but not limited to, any claims arising in connection with the use or disclosure of your personal information by any third party not under the direct control of MockBank

_Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors_

Our site contains links to other sites whose information and security practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy policies, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

_Cookies_

To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

_Our Commitment to Security_

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. While MockBank strives to protect your personal information, it cannot guarantee or warrant the security of the information you transmit to us, and if you choose to use our Site, you do so at your own risk. MockBank has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. Only authorized employees have access to the information you provide us. There are strict rules on all authorized persons who have access either to the databases that store user information or to the servers that host our services. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we make every effort to prevent such unfortunate occurrences.

_Illegal Use_

Using www.MockBank.com to transmit any material (by email, instant messaging, posting or otherwise) that, intentionally or unintentionally, violates any applicable local, state, national, international law, or any rules or regulations promulgated hereunder is prohibited.
